<XML>
<VACANCIES><VAC><RUBR_ID>90</RUBR_ID><VAC_NAME>Creative Director / Senior Producer</VAC_NAME><VAC_TEXT>Creative Director / Senior Producer (CG Art, Animation, FMV)

Position Objective:

Large well-established studio needs a Creative Director / Senior Producer (CG Art, Animation, and FMV). You will be responsible for creating and tuning art process for different kinds of art work. You will work with the Lead Artists and Team of Artists in the different projects. The Creative Director / Senior Producer will report to the Senior Management in all aspects of conceiving and developing high-quality, commercially successful games and movies art assets. 

Principle Responsibilities:
o	Responsible for directing the art development of multiple projects.
o	Ensure that all necessary assets and materials are delivered to Customer on schedule with required quality; setup and maintain QA processes.
o	Scout out, evaluate, and hire developers.
o	Generate ideas for new products and manage concepts review and evaluation.


Background and Knowledge:
Х	5 years prior interactive media work experience.
Х	Excellent working knowledge of character animation tools and setup environment in Maya.
Х	Assisted in the production of at least 2 interactive titles from beginning to end and understands the technical process of game development.
Х	3D computer graphics programming experience or education is desirable.
Х	Experience with Special/Visual Effects is a plus.
Х	Experience with character animation tools and setup environment in Softimage is desirable.
Х	Worked within and understands the importance of maintaining production schedules, project management tools, databases and deadlines.
Х	Extensive knowledge of video games.

Core Competencies:
Х	Fluent English
Х	Great Communicator: Strong verbal communication and writing skills
Х	Creative and responsible.
Х	Works well within a tightly knit team under tight schedules.
Х	Ability to juggle several tasks simultaneously and to work on more than one project at a time effectively.
Х	Knowledge of basic productivity software such as Word, Excel, and MS Project, as well as computer graphics programs and formats that are integral to interactive game development and FMV production.

Please, send your letter to  info@PershaStudia.com with stated: 1) in Subject line УCreative Director [21]Ф, 2) Full name, 3) contact phones, 4) e-mail address. </VAC_TEXT></VAC><VAC><RUBR_ID>90</RUBR_ID><VAC_NAME>ѕрограммист - Developer [Flash (ActionScript), Director (Lingo)]</VAC_NAME><VAC_TEXT>¬ компании занимающейс€ разработкой 3D WEB систем, открыта  нова€  ваканси€ дл€ программиста. ќт кандидата требуетс€  профессиональное знание и владение Macromedia Flash (профессиональное владение Action Script), очень желательно знание Macromedia Director (Lingo),  так же плюсом €вл€етс€ опыт работы с Flash Communication Server, Java. «нание английского €зыка. –азмер заработной платы по результатам собеседовани€. —вои резюме высылать на okotkov@mywebfit.com</VAC_TEXT></VAC><VAC><RUBR_ID>90</RUBR_ID><VAC_NAME>техник-электронщик</VAC_NAME><VAC_TEXT>“ребуетс€ техник-электронщик в сервисный центр по ремонту мобильных телефнов</VAC_TEXT></VAC><VAC><RUBR_ID>90</RUBR_ID><VAC_NAME>Software Testing Engineer</VAC_NAME><VAC_TEXT>УCelenia Software Ukraine Ltd.Ф is a fast-growing international software company. Having been stable and successful for a long period we are working in close cooperation with Microsoft Business Solutions. We are having many exciting projects in the Navision and Axapta product areas which demand that Celenia is constantly growing and developing.
We offer a challenging career opportunity and excellent professional environment for your growth as a Software Testing Engineer. 
We expect you to have:	
Х	Good command of English (mandatory)
Х	Technical and programming background
Х	Understanding of the automated software testing (experience with any test tool; Visual      
            test or AQdev team, is a plus)
Х	At least one year of experience as a software testing engineer
Х	Experience with the ERP-class systems
Х	Knowledge of C++, VB, OOD, UML, XML, .Net
Х	At least half a year experience as a software developer
We guarantee:
Х	Excellent career opportunities
Х	Social package
Х	Competitive salary that will be discussed at the Interview
Х	English lessons conducted by native speaker
Х	Microsoft certification
Х	Trainings 
Please send your detailed CVs in English for our consideration at ste@celenia.com stating the position, or call Anna Isayeva at (044)-568-51-11. Successful candidates will be contacted regarding time for the interview.
</VAC_TEXT></VAC><VAC><RUBR_ID>90</RUBR_ID><VAC_NAME>программист 1—</VAC_NAME><VAC_TEXT>¬озраст до 40 лет, муж/жен., ќ¬, необходимы навыки в разработке программного обеспечени€ на базе 1—:ѕредпри€тие 7.х., знание основ бух.учета, некнофликтность, умение работать в команде.</VAC_TEXT></VAC></VACANCIES>
</XML>